<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>AppVisor 1.0.43</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>http://publisher.appvisor.com</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD(TM) 2004 Association of Software Professionals (ASP)http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad is a data set standard and specification that is commercialsoftware publishers to disseminate certified information about their software application. The PAD format is copyright of the ASP and cannot be used without the formal licensing and permission of both the Association of Software Professionals and its agent AppVisor.com.</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
    <CERTIFIED>No</CERTIFIED>
    <CERTIFICATE_ID></CERTIFICATE_ID>
    <CERTIFICATE_LICENSE></CERTIFICATE_LICENSE>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
  <RoboSoft>
    <Company_UIN>CMP-6500FA922770</Company_UIN>
    <Product_UIN>APP-7500FA922770</Product_UIN>
    <Publish_on_CD></Publish_on_CD>
    <NewsFeed_Search_String></NewsFeed_Search_String>
    <Search_String></Search_String>
    <Press_Release_Search_String></Press_Release_Search_String>
    <Backlink></Backlink>
    <Comments_For_Reviewer></Comments_For_Reviewer>
    <Search_String_Unique></Search_String_Unique>
    <Search_Engine_Search_String></Search_Engine_Search_String>
    <Web_Directories_Search_String></Web_Directories_Search_String>
    <Company_Description></Company_Description>
  </RoboSoft>
  <Company_Info>
    <PublisherID>pid-a3002f986270</PublisherID>
    <BrandID>bid-6500fa922770</BrandID>
    <Company_Name>K치roly Pados</Company_Name>
    <Country>Hungary</Country>
    <State_Province></State_Province>
    <City_Town></City_Town>
    <Zip_Postal_Code></Zip_Postal_Code>
    <Address_1></Address_1>
    <Address_2></Address_2>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>http://tinywall.pados.hu</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_Info>
      <Contact_First_Name>K치roly</Contact_First_Name>
      <Contact_Last_Name>Pados</Contact_Last_Name>
      <Contact_Email>tinywall@pados.hu</Contact_Email>
      <Author_First_Name>K치roly</Author_First_Name>
      <Author_Last_Name>Pados</Author_Last_Name>
      <Author_Email></Author_Email>
      <Contact_Phone></Contact_Phone>
    </Contact_Info>
    <Support_Info>
      <Sales_Email>tinywall@pados.hu</Sales_Email>
      <Support_Email>tinywall@pados.hu</Support_Email>
      <General_Email>tinywall@pados.hu</General_Email>
      <Sales_Phone></Sales_Phone>
      <Support_Phone></Support_Phone>
      <General_Phone></General_Phone>
      <Fax_Phone></Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
    <GooglePlusPage></GooglePlusPage>
    <LinkedinPage></LinkedinPage>
    <TwitterCompanyPage></TwitterCompanyPage>
    <FacebookCompanyPage></FacebookCompanyPage>
    <CompanyStorePage></CompanyStorePage>
  </Company_Info>
  <Program_Info>
    <AppID>app-7500fa922770</AppID>
    <Program_Name>TinyWall</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>2.1.3</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>07</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>12</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2013</Program_Release_Year>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>0</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code></Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Cost_Other></Program_Cost_Other>
    <Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Category_Class>Security &amp; Privacy::Access Control</Program_Category_Class>
    <Program_Specific_Category>Utilities</Program_Specific_Category>
    <Program_Categories>Internet :: Firewalls,Security Tools :: Personal Firewalls,Internet :: Security,Utilities :: System Utilities</Program_Categories>
    <Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
    <Program_OS_Support>Win7 x32,Win7 x64,Windows 8,WinVista,WinVista x64</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English,Dutch,French,German,Hungarian,Japanese,Portuguese,Russian,Spanish</Program_Language>
    <Program_Change_Info>See http://tinywall.pados.hu/changelog.txt</Program_Change_Info>
    <Program_System_Requirements>Microsoft .Net Framework 3.5 SP1</Program_System_Requirements>
    <Limitations>None</Limitations>
    <Awards></Awards>
    <File_Info>
      <File_Size_Bytes>1163264</File_Size_Bytes>
      <File_Size_K>1136</File_Size_K>
      <File_Size_MB>1.11</File_Size_MB>
      <Filename_Versioned></Filename_Versioned>
      <Filename_Previous></Filename_Previous>
      <Filename_Generic></Filename_Generic>
      <Filename_Long></Filename_Long>
    </File_Info>
    <Expire_Info>
      <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
      <Expire_Count></Expire_Count>
      <Expire_Based_On></Expire_Based_On>
      <Expire_Year></Expire_Year>
      <Expire_Other_Info></Expire_Other_Info>
      <Expire_Month></Expire_Month>
      <Expire_Day></Expire_Day>
    </Expire_Info>
    <FacebookFanPage></FacebookFanPage>
    <VideoLink1URL></VideoLink1URL>
    <VideoLink2URL></VideoLink2URL>
    <Includes_JAVA_VM></Includes_JAVA_VM>
    <Includes_DirectX></Includes_DirectX>
    <Includes_VB_Runtime></Includes_VB_Runtime>
    <GooglePlusFanPage></GooglePlusFanPage>
  </Program_Info>
  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>http://tinywall.pados.hu/</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>http://tinywall.pados.hu/</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>http://tinywall.pados.hu/PAD/tinywall_menu.jpg</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>http://tinywall.pados.hu/PAD/tinywall_icon.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
      <Application_XML_File_URL>http://tinywall.pados.hu/PAD/pad_file.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>http://tinywall.pados.hu/ccount/click.php?id=3</Primary_Download_URL>
      <Secondary_Download_URL></Secondary_Download_URL>
      <Additional_Download_URL_1></Additional_Download_URL_1>
      <Additional_Download_URL_2></Additional_Download_URL_2>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>
  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>
      <Keywords>firewall,security,protection,privacy,network</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>A lightweight, non-intrusive firewall</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Harden and control the firewall built into Windows with ease, without annoyance</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>TinyWall hardens and controls the firewall built into Windows, but does not display popups. Instead, TinyWall allows users to whitelist or unblock programs via various other innovative methods. Designed to be simple to use, secure and non-intrusive.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>TinyWall hardens and controls the firewall built into Windows, but does not display popups. Instead, TinyWall allows users to whitelist or unblock programs via various other innovative methods.Designed to be simple to use, secure and non-intrusive. TinyWall provides firewall tampering protection, supports password lock, multiple firewall modes, automatic learning, blocklists and many other features that make it a unique firewall.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Designed to harden and control the advanced firewall built into Windows, TinyWall includes a combination of features that sets it apart from both commercial and freeware firewalls.

TinyWall does not display popups that "urge users to allow". In fact, it will not notify you of any blocked action. Rather than displaying popups, TinyWall allows users to whitelist or unblock programs via various methods. For example, you can just initiate whitelisting by a hotkey, then click on a window that you want to allow. Or, you can select an application from the list of running processes. (Of course, the traditional way of selecting an executable also works.)

This approach avoids popups but still keeps the firewall very easy to use. It will also limit the list of unblocked programs to those that the user really needs, which is optimal from a security standpoint.

TinyWall gives Windows Firewall a sane and secure configuration and presents you with a simple interface where you can easily define what has network access and what not, while preventing other programs from modifing or overwriting your firewall settings.

Key features:
- TinyWall lets you work while protecting you. There are no annoying popups but configuration is very simple.
- Using the advanced Windows Firewall built into newer Windows versions, TinyWall's performance impact is neglible.
- No drivers or kernel-components are installed so it does not influence system stability.
- Automatic learning, blocklists, password lock, firewall tampering protection and built-in tight firewall rules help increase TinyWall's and your computer's security even further.
- Firewall modes and lots of other convenience features make TinyWall extremely easy to use for anybody.
- All packed into a download that is about a megabyte.

Requires Microsoft .Net Framework 3.5 SP1 or newer.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </English>
  </Program_Descriptions>
  <Permissions>
    <Distribution_Permissions>Distributors must too also abide by the EULA. See EULA for terms on distribution.</Distribution_Permissions>
    <EULA>END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT ("EULA")

Definition of SOFTWARE: This installer and all components of TinyWall, 
including but not limited to executables, media, documentation and 
databases installed by this installer.

Definition of AUTHOR: K치roly Pados and copyright holders

IMPORTANT-READ CAREFULLY: This End-User License Agreement ("EULA") is a 
legal agreement between you (either an individual or a single entity) and 
AUTHOR. By installing, copying, or otherwise using the SOFTWARE, you 
agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA. If you do not agree to the 
terms of this EULA, do not install or use the SOFTWARE.

 1. Freeware
 You may use the SOFTWARE without charge.

 2. Distribution of SOFTWARE.
You may make copies of the SOFTWARE as you wish; give exact copies of the 
original SOFTWARE to anyone; and distribute the SOFTWARE in its 
unmodified form via electronic means. You may not charge any fees for the 
copy or use of the SOFTWARE itself. You must not represent in any way 
that you are selling the SOFTWARE itself. Your distribution of the 
SOFTWARE will not entitle you to any compensation from AUTHOR.  You must 
distribute a copy of this EULA with any copy of the SOFTWARE and anyone 
to whom you distribute the SOFTWARE is subject to this EULA.

 3. RESTRICTIONS
3.1 You may not reverse engineer, de-compile, or disassemble the SOFTWARE.
3.2 You may not rent, lease, or lend the SOFTWARE.
3.3 You may permanently transfer all of your rights under this EULA, 
provided the recipient agrees to the terms of this EULA. 
3.4 You may not use the SOFTWARE to perform any unauthorized transfer of 
information or for any illegal purpose.
3.5 You may not repackage the software or provide alternate installers 
whose main purpose is to install the SOFTWARE.

 4. NO WARRANTIES
AUTHOR expressly disclaims any warranty for the SOFTWARE. THE SOFTWARE IS 
PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, 
INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR MERCHANTABILITY, 
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NONINFRINGEMENT. THE ENTIRE RISK 
ARISING OUT OF USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE SOFTWARE REMAINS WITH YOU. IN NO 
EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, 
DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR 
OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE 
USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</EULA>
  </Permissions>
  <Site>
    <Site_FORM></Site_FORM>
    <Site_VERSION></Site_VERSION>
    <Site_URL></Site_URL>
    <Site_DESCRIPTION></Site_DESCRIPTION>
    <Site_Site_Title>TinyWall</Site_Site_Title>
    <Site_Site_URL>http://tinywall.pados.hu</Site_Site_URL>
    <Site_Keywords>tinywall,internet,firewall,security</Site_Keywords>
    <Site_Description_100>TinyWall's official website</Site_Description_100>
    <Site_Description_250></Site_Description_250>
    <Site_Description_450></Site_Description_450>
    <Site_Contact_First_Name></Site_Contact_First_Name>
    <Site_Contact_Last_Name></Site_Contact_Last_Name>
    <Site_Contact_Email></Site_Contact_Email>
  </Site>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
